janae.stewart94@gmail.com • LinkedIn: Janae Stewart

PROFILE

Expertise: Social media marketing – setup, strategy, development, management, content creation, and advertising. Websites – usability, development, search engine optimization, and addons. PPC advertising. Video editing & photography.

Technical skills: Social Media Networking, proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Troubleshooting, WordPress, Google AdWords Certified, Google Ads Search Certified, Lightroom, Photoshop

RELATED WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Photographer

January 2020 - Present

- Contributed to the following online publications: Unclear Magazine, Dark Matter Publications, and Anti Magazine
- Photographed various musical artists at notable venues such as: Brooklyn Steel

Internship | Mixdown Studios.

June 2019 - Present

- Manage all aspects of the advertising, marketing, promotional activities for the business including optimal placements for ads, email promotions and search engine via Google Ads campaigns and Video ads
- Manage visual content for Hometown Heroes' online marketing strategy; implementing photography expertise to develop AdWords marketing materials and promotional items
- Create a strong, visible social media presence and develop concepts/content with viral potential. Continuously monitor online public relations with biweekly Instagram live streams
- Develop a strong working foundation of several image editing software such as Photoshop,
 Canva, Adobe Spark Post, and Lightroom to create posts for social media
- Establish a network of communication and collaboration with management to develop a competent and objective-driven environment

Internship | WISE: Women's Islamic Initiative in Spirituality and Equality June 2019 - March 2020

- Created visual materials to show donors their impact which resulted in an additional \$10,000 in donations
- Supervised and directly implement SEO practices for different pages for the company website including developing SEO keywords for individual pages and working with the add-on Yoast
- Created a PowerPoint deck that was present for the United States Institute of Peace discussion to over 50 people
- Served as a key subject matter expert for website development working on the backend of the WordPress website: editing and adding vital content
- Created the basis for a marketing plan. Including the outlining of a schedule plan and coming up with initiatives to promote a new awareness campaign

EDUCATION/CERTIFICATIONS

Boston University School of Management

May 2016

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration Concentration of Finance Google AdWords Certified, Google Ads Search Certification